let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Node.js is written in",
      answer: "JavaScript",
      options: [
        "JavaScript",
        "C",
        "C++",
        "All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "How modules in Node.js can be connected from one component to another?",
      answer: "Exports",
      options: [
        "Expose",
        "Module",
        "Exports",
        "All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the below modules is not a built-in module in Node.js?",
      answer: "fsread",
      options: [
        "zlib",
        "HTTPS",
        "dgram",
        "fsread"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the below command will show all the modules installed locally?",
      answer: "npm ls",
      options: [
        "npm ls -g",
        "npm ls",
        "node ls -g",
        "node ls"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the below fs module is used to truncate a file?",
      answer: "fs.ftruncate(fd, len, callback)",
      options: [
        "fs.delete(fd, len, callback)",
        "fs.remove(fd, len, callback)",
        "fs.ftruncate(fd, len, callback)",
        "None of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which template engines can be used with Node.js?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      options: [
        "Jade",
        "Vash",
        "Handlebars",
        "All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "How do we return a path string from the given path object in Node.js?",
      answer: "path.format()",
      options: [
        "path.get()",
        "path.set()",
        "path.format()",
        "path.return()"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is the default scope in the Node.js application?",
      answer: "Global",
      options: [
        "Global",
        "Local",
        "Global Function",
        "Local to object"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the below method is used to return the current working directory of the process?",
      answer: "cwd()",
      options: [
        "cwd()",
        "cmd()",
        "pwd()",
        "None of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which below method is used to check whether the given path is an absolute path or not in Node.js?",
      answer: "path.isAbsolute()",
      options: [
        "path.Query()",
        "path.render()",
        "Tick",
        "path.isAbsolute()",
        "path.Absolute()"
      ]
    },  
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable “a” is not equal the “NULL”",
      answer: "if(a!==null)",
      options: [
        "if(a!==null)",
        "if (a!)",
        "if(a!=null)",
        "if(a!null)"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "The “function” and ” var” are known as",
      answer: "Declaration statements",
      options: [
        "Keywords",
        "Data types",
        "Prototypes",
        "Declaration statements"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "Suppose we have a text “human” that we want to convert into string without using the “new” operator. Which is the correct way from the following to do so",
      answer: "Both human.toString() and String(human)",
      options: [
        "String newvariable=”human”",
        "String(human)",
        "toString()",
        "Both human.toString() and String(human)"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression",
      answer: "Function literal",
      options: [
        "Function literal",
        "Function calling",
        "Function prototype",
        "Function declaration"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "Which of the following one is the property of the primary expression",
      answer: "stand-alone expressions",
      options: [
        "contains variable references alone",
        "Contains only keywords",
        "basic expressions containing all necessary functions",
        "stand-alone expressions"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "Which one of the following is used for the calling a function or a method in the JavaScript",
      answer: "Invocation expression",
      options: [
        "Invocation expression",
        "Functional expression",
        "Property Access Expression",
        "Primary expression"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do",
      answer: "Ignores the statements",
      options: [
        "Throws an error",
        "Prompts to complete the statement",
        "Shows a warning",
        "Ignores the statements"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "The “new Point(3,2)”, is a kind of _______ expression",
      answer: "Object Creation Expression",
      options: [
        "Invocation Expression",
        "Primary Expression",
        "Object Creation Expression",
        "Constructor Calling Expression"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "Which one of the following operator is used to check weather a specific property exists or not",
      answer: "in",
      options: [
        "in",
        "exist",
        "Exists",
        "within"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "What if we define a “for” loop and it removes one of the properties that has not yet been enumerated?",
      answer: "That specific property will not be enumerated",
      options: [
        "The loop will not run at all",
        "The removed property will be stored in a cache",
        "That property will be enumerated",
        "That specific property will not be enumerated"
      ]
    },
  ];